

NASHWAN Δ.ΚΗΔΙΔΕ

Email: nashwan a89@yahoo.com

Mobile: +9647716315698

Address: Iraq/Baghdad



Nashwan Al Moussawi



Nashwan Abdul ameer

ABOUT ME

I have started my career in ALKHAN Co. in Mid-2014, since then my work tended to focus on construction coordination and architectural design and details. In 2015, I was employed by E.C.O. Itd as a professional designer, extensively trained and started using BIM-tools for construction projects. In line with this scope, I was hired by AI Nahda Co. later the same year, in which BIMM was fully integrated in their workflow including Energy Analysis, in which I was entitled to design and assess with a specialized team.

EDUCATION

2009 - 2014 University of Technology, BSc Architectural Engineering Department

Key Modules: Design Thesis, Architectural Details, Project Management, Building Regulation, Quantities and Specifications, Design Thesis Research, Philosophy and Architecture, and Sustainable Architecture

EXPERIENCE

2014 - 2015 Working in ALKHAN CO.,

a coordinator and drafting in ALNEHRWAN HOUSING PROJECT

2015 - 2019 Working in AL NAHDA CO,

designing and 'planning

2019 to present time Working in (KOREA AEROSPACE INDUSTRIES, LTD.)

SKILLS

Autodesk Revit



Photoshop



Autodesk AutoCAD





Microsoft Project Adobe Indisgen •••



Microsoft Word

Autodesk 3Ds Studio Max



LANGUAGES

Arabic (Native)

English (Fluent).

MEMBERSHIPS

Licensed Architect since 2015, IEU (Iraqi engineering Union)